好了，我们已经实现了contentprovider的核心，
Well we're done with the core of our content provider,
但是仍然有一个可选的方法，它能够让代码变得
but there's still one more optional method that'll make things
更加高效。我们通过Ctrl+O开始看
much more efficient. We'll start by hitting Ctrl+O to look
我们能够重写的函数。目前显示有
at the functions we can override. It turns out there's
一个函数叫bulkInsert。任何以前做过
a function called bulkInsert. Anyone out there who has done
数据库工作的人知道在
database work knows that putting a bunch of inserts into
一个事务插入一堆数据经常要比一个一个插入更快。
a single transaction is usually much faster than inserting them
BulkInsert允许我们做这件事。默认的
individually. Bulk insert allows us to do just that. The default
实现是只多次调用insert，但是
implementation just calls insert a bunch of times, but
我们能够将它放在一个事务，如果我们实现
we can wrap it in a transaction if we implement
它。我们只是将在这添加
it ourselves. We're only going to add support for
天气预测事务的支持，因为只有他们是一批一起添加的。
weather forecast transactions here, since they're the only we insert
我们以调用db.beginTransaction开始。对于每个
in bulk. We start by calling db.beginTransaction. For each
传入的contentvalues，我们插入和更新插入记录的个数。
ContentValues passed in, we insert and update the number of
当我们做完了，我们设置事务
records inserted. When we're done, we set the transaction
成功。否则，我们的记录将不会提交
to be successful. Otherwise our records will not be committed,
并且将依赖最后的结束事务的语句。
and then rely on the finally statement to end the
默认情况，我们只是调用超类。
transaction. In the default case, we just call the super
记住，它做了插入，但并不是那么完美。
class. Remember, it does the insert, just not optimally. And
好了，这就是我们实现的bulkInsert。
that's it, that's all we have to do to implement bulkInsert.